Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Buttons and Memorabilia Collection, 1940-1990 IBT0057
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Miscellaneous Acquisitions, 1872-2013; Series 4
  - Miscellaneous Memorabilia Items, 1903-2008; Series 4 Subseries 5
    - IBT Logo Plastic Plaque, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 258)
    - Maritime Union of Australia Cufflinks, 1993; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 259a-b)
    - Local 2 Foam Cup Cozy, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 260)
    - Numo Manufacturing Foam Disk, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 261)
    - Teamsters Logo Plastic Wallet, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 262)
    - IBT 26th Internatinoal Convention Freight Division Luggage Tags, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 263a-b)
    - "Dime Delivery" Embroidered Patch, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 264)
    - "Associated Safe Driver 13 Years" Embroidered Patch, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 265)
    - Local 135 Sticker, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 266)
    - "TDU Sucks" Stickers, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 267)
    - IBT Lanyards, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 268a-f)
    - Star-shaped IBT Logo Foam Stress Ball, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 269)
    - Michigan Teamsters Joint Council 43 Money Clip, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Item 1)
    - IBT Logo/Jimmy Hoffa Metal Business Card Holder, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Item 2)
    - International Union of Painters and Allied Trades Local 880 Mini Screwdriver, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Item 3)
    - Teamsters Warehouse Division Pen, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Item 4)
    - Local 135 Pens, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Item 5a-f)
    - Neon Yellow/Blue IBT Pens, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Item 6a-c)
    - "Build Union Buy Union" American Flag Sticker, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Item 7)
    - "Buy Union Buy American" American Flag Sticker, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Item 8)
    - Local 120 Sticker, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Item 9)
    - Local 471 25th Anniversary Souvenir Badge, 1937; Series 4 (Box 11, Item 10)
    - Michelle Gopman Visitor Badge for 26th Area Conference of Southern Conference of Teamsters, 1980; Series 4 (Box 11, Item 11)
    - Mrs. John T. Obrien Guest Badge for 5th Conference of Eastern Conference of Teamsters, 1958; Series 4 (Box 11, Item 12)
    - Executive Committee Medal for Chicago Federation of Labor Celebration, Labor Day 1947, Series 4 (Box 11, Item 13)
    - Henry D. Lloyd Memorial Committee (Nov 1903) Ribbon, Series 4 (Box 11, Item 14)
    - Thomas E. Flynn Delegate Badge for ALA Founding Conference 1969, Series 4 (Box 11, Item 15)
    - John T. O'Briend Delegate Medal for Illinois State Federation of Labor Conference, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Item 16)
    - Illinois State Industrial Union Council Medal, Undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Item 17)
    - Guest Medal for 19th IBT Convention 1966, Series 4 (Box 11, Item 18a-b)
    - Delegate Pin for 32nd Annual Convention of American Federation of Labor, 1912, Series 4 (Box 11, Item 19)
    - American Fedeartion of Labor/Seal of City of Rochester Medal, 1912; Series 4 (Box 11, Item 20)
    - Guest Medal for 64th Annual Convention of American Fedeartion of Labor 1944, Series 4 (Box 11, Item 21)
    - Delegate Badge for 55th Annual Convention of American Federation of Labor, 1935, Series 4 (Box 11, Item 22)
    - Delegate Medal for 42nd Annual American Federation of Labor Conference, 1922, Series 4 (Box 11, Item 23)
    - Guest Medal for 59th Annual Convention of American Federation of Labor, 1939, Series 4 (Box 11, Item 24)
    - American Federation of Labor Conference Medal, 1910, Series 4 (Box 11, Item 25)
    - Delegate Medal for American Federation of Labor 57th Annual Convention, 1937, Series 4 (Box 11, Item 26)
    - Delegate Medal for American Federation of Labor 58th Convention, 1938, Series 4 (Box 11, Item 27)
    - Frank Brown Medal for American Legion 19th Convention, 1937, Series 4 (Box 11, Item 28)
    - 4th Annual Picnic of Packing House Teamsters Ribbon, 1909; Series 4 (Box 11, Item 29)
    - Teamster's National Hispanic Caucus Mousepad "Adelante!", ND; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - International Brotherhood of Teamsters 2007-2008 Calendar, Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - International Brotherhood of Teamsters 100th Anniversary Calendar, 1903-2003, Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 21st Convention - Las Vegas, Nevada, 1975 - 1976; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Blank IBT Letterhead, President James R. Hoffa, 1957 - 1971; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - A Look at Your Union Booklet, ND; Series 4, Subseries 5 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - IBT Sponsored Bumper Stickers, ND; Series 4, Subseries 5 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Sixty-Two Years of Progress - Anniversary Ball and Year Book, Draymen and Teamsters Benevolent Society, October 21, 1939; Series 4, Subseries 5 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - The president's Medal Ceremony Honoring James P. Hoffa at George Washington University, January 29, 2014; Series 4, Subseries 5 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - 50th Anniversary of the Trucking Industry Stamp, IBT0057 Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - National Teamster Headquarters Postcard, ND; IBT 0057 Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Buy American Stamp, 1933; IBT 0057 Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - 150th Anniversary Pin Folder, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box Shared Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Bumper Stickers, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box Shared Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Fred 2016 Teamsters United!, Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box Shared Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Textiles and Associated Material, 1872-2013; Series 4 Subseries 6
    - "Bierbrauer Unterstutzungs Verein, Gegrundet 1872, Cleveland, Ohio" Satin Banner with Tassels, Series 4 Subseries 6 (Box 6, Item 1)
    - "Sergeant at Arms" Blue and Yellow Armband, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 6 (Box 6, Item 2)
    - IBT Logo Flag, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 6 (Box 6, Item 3)
    - Teamster Women's Conference 2013 Mardi Gras Themed T-Shirt, Series 4 Subseries 6 (Box 6, Item 4)
    - "The Teamster Women's 2013 Conference" Tote Bag containing Notebook, Program, and "James P. Hoffa Remembered" Memorial Book, Series 4 Subseries 6 (Box 6, Item 5a-d)
    - IBT Staff Vest, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 6 (Box 6, Item 6)
    - "Teamsters for Obama" Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 6 (Box 6, Item 7)
      General
      Associated with IBT Staff Vest
    - Local 670 (Nov 1934) Button, Series 4 Subseries 6 (Box 6, Item 8)
    - "Restore the Power" Hoffa/Hogan/Young Button, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 6 (Box 6, Item 9)
    - Local 20 Steward Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 6 (Box 6, Item 10)
    - Teamster Logo "Women" Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 6 (Box 6, Item 11)
    - "We Support Our Troops" Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 6 (Box 6, Item 12)
    - "JRHMSF Celebrating 10 Years" Lapel Pin, 2009; Series 4 Subseries 6 (Box 6, Item 13)
    - National Safety Council 7 Year Safe Driver Award Embroidered Patch, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 6 (Box 6, Item 14)
    - Local Union 20 Lanyard, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 6 (Box 6, Item 15)
    - Teamster Logo Patches and Sticker, ND, IBT 0057 Series 4 Sub Series 6 (Box Shared Box 34, Folder 5)
- Gift of Cheryl Johnson, 1981-2006; Series 5
  - Roy Williams/"Jackie" Presser Election Button, 1981; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 1)
  - Mondale/Ferraro Button, 1984; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 2)
  - "We Won!" Teamsters for Clinton Button, 1992; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 3)
  - R.V. Durham Unity Team Staff Button, 1991; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 4)
  - R.V. Durham Unity Team Button, 1991; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 5)
  - "Don't Blame Me, I Voted for R. V." Button, 1991; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 6a-b)
  - R.V. Durham/Harold Leu Unity Team Button, 1991; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 7)
  - "I Voted for the R. V. Durham Unity Team" Button, 1991; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 8)
  - Bill Clinton - America's Star Button, 1996; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 9)
  - "Ohio for Clinton/Gore" Button, 1996; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 10)
  - Clinton/Gore '96 Button, 1996; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 11)
  - "Teamsters for Clinton" Button, 1996; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 12)
  - America's First Lady - Hillary Clinton Button, 1996; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 13)
  - Teamsters for Clinton Portrait Button, 1996; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 14)
  - "Make America Work Again" Teamsters for Clinton/Gore Button, 1996; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 15)
  - Rosie the Riveter Clinton/Gore Button, 1996; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 16)
  - Dave Leland Support Clinton For President, Ohio Button, 1996; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 17)
  - Hillary Clinton Heart-Shaped Button, 1996; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 18)
  - "Hoffa '96 Restore the Power" Buttons, 1996; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 19a-b)
  - "Action! Motown '97 Detroit Michigan" Button, 1997; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 20)
  - Alfred K. Whitehead Tribute Dinner Button, 2000; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 21)
  - Cheryl Johnson's Teamster Women Conference Button - Las Vegas, 2000; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 22)
  - Hoffa 2001 Buttons, Series 5 (Box 7, Item 23a-d)
  - Never Forget - September 11 Button, 2001; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 24)
  - Local 435 (2002) Button, Series 5 (Box 7, Item 25)
  - Cheryl Jonsohn Exhibitor Button for Minnesota Union Industries Show, 2002; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 26)
  - Vote Team Lichtenwald Button, 2004; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 27)
  - "Si Se Puede" J. Gilberto Soto Button, 2004; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 28)
  - Hoffa/Keegel/Wood Vote 2006 Button, Series 5 (Box 7, Item 29)
  - Hoffa/Coli 2006 Button, Series 5 (Box 7, Item 30)
  - Hoffa/Flynn 2006 Button, Series 5 (Box 7, Item 31)
  - Hoffa 2006 Button, Series 5 (Box 7, Item 32)
  - Cheryl Johnson Teamster Women Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 33)
  - "Teamster Women on the Move for Good Jobs and a Better Future" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 36)
  - "Woman Organizers Rock!" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 38a-b)
  - "Teamster Women Make a Difference" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 39)
  - "International Teamster Women's Caucus" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 40)
  - "A Woman's Place is In Her Union" Neon Pink Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 41)
  - "A Woman's Place is in Her Union" Local 696 Rose Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 42)
  - "A Woman's Place is in Her Union" Pink IBT Logo Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 43)
  - Teamsters Women American/Canadian Flag Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 44)
  - "A Woman's Place is in Her Union" Gold Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 45)
  - "I'm a Friend of Jimmy Hoffa" Small Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 46)
  - "I'm a Friend of Jimmy Hoffa" Large Buttons, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 47a-c)
  - "I'm a Friend of Jimmy Hoffa" Portrait Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 48)
  - "Jimmy Hoffa for a Kick Ass Union" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 49)
  - Local 20 "Vote Teamster - Insure Your Future" Buttons, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 50a-c)
  - "I Voted for America" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 51)
  - "Vote Teamsters" Neon Green Buttons, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 52a-b)
  - "Vote Teamster for a Better Future" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 53)
  - "The New Teamsters for Good Jobs and a Better Future" Buttons, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 54a-b)
  - Local Unity! Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 55)
  - Union Yes Buttons, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 56a-b)
  - "Drive - Democrat, Republican, Independent Voter Education" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 57)
  - "Proud To Be a Teamster" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 58)
  - "Diversity Matters - Human Rights Commission" Rainbow Logo Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 59)
  - "Diversity Matters - Human Rights Commission" Blue Logo Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Item 60)
  - "Teamsters National Training" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 1)
  - "A Nickel an Hour for Teamster Power" Buttons, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 2a-b)
  - "Solidarity Day '91" Washington, DC Button, 1991; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 3)
  - "Teamsters 1st" Buttons, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 4a-b)
  - "Join ITWC" International Teamster Women's Caucus Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 5)
  - "Give 'em Health Hillary" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 6)
  - "Stop Scabs" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 7)
  - Scab Hunter Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 8)
  - "UPS Show me the Money" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 9)
  - Flush Rush Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 10)
  - "S-55 Now" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 11)
  - "Gimme Five! Support H.R. 5 and S. 55" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 12)
  - "I Support Mental Health Issue 5" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 13)
  - "I Support U.A.W. - We Will Not Break" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 14)
  - Calvin TDU Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 15)
  - "The L. E. U. Team" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 16)
  - "Teamsters Support the Troops" Ohio Conference Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 17)
  - "Bill Bradley for President" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 18)
  - "Experience and Leadership - Re-relect LEU" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 19)
  - "Rush for President" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 20)
  - Anti-Carey Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 21)
  - "Impeach Ron Carey/TDU Sucks" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 22)
  - "I'm for the Bill Hogan Team" Buttons, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 23a-b)
  - "Mozena/Slate Yes" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 24)
  - "Teamsters for Ferner" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 25)
  - "Still America's First Family" John F. Kennedy and Jackie Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 26)
  - Teamsters Local 20 "The Elite Club - Les Singer, President" Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 27)
  - Local 20, Toledo OH Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 28)
  - Local 237 IBT Logo Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 29)
  - Local 202 Steward Button, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 30)
  - Local 20 Buttons, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 31a-b)
  - "Jackie Presser 81" Lapel Pins, 1981; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 32a-b)
  - 98th Tournament of Roses Lapel Pin, 1987; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 33)
  - "Dianne '90" Lapel Pin, 1990; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 34)
  - IBT 24th International Convention Lapel Pin, 1991; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 35a-b)
  - "Kodak '92" Olympic Rings Lapel Pin, 1992; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 36)
  - "H '96" Lapel Pin, 1996; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 37)
  - Local 63 25th Anniversary Lapel Pin, 2000; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 38a-c)
  - "The Voice of American Labor - Teamsters Vote 2000" Lapel Pin, Series 5 (Box 8, Item 39)
  - "Gore/Lieberman 2000" Lapel Pins, Series 5 (Box 8, Item 40a-b)
  - Gore 2000 Lapel Pin, Series 5 (Box 8, Item 41)
  - IBT Convention 2001 Lapel Pin, Series 5 (Box 8, Item 42)
  - "Hoffa 2001 Unity Slate" Lapel Pin, Series 5 (Box 8, Item 43)
  - IBT 100 Years, 1903-2003 Lapel Pin, Series 5 (Box 8, Item 44a-b)
  - BLE PAC President's Club Lapel Pin, 2003; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 46)
  - "Hoffa" IBT Logo Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 46)
  - Hoffa/Hogan Restore the Pride Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 47)
  - IBT Logo Canadian Maple Leaf Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 48)
  - Canadian Maple Leaf Black IBT Logo Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 49)
  - Teamsters Canada Maple Leaf Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 50)
  - Gold Borderered Canadian Maple Leaf IBT Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 51)
  - International Teamster Women's Caucus American/Canadian Flag Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 52a-b)
  - Canadian Flag Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 53)
  - "Durham" American and Canadian Flags Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 54)
  - ITWC 1st Covention, Las Vegas NV Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 55)
  - Construction Council of Ontario IBT Logo Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 56)
  - IBT Public Service Division Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 57)
  - IBT Chicago Hispanic Caucus Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 58)
  - Teamsters Hispanic Caucus Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 59)
  - Teamsters Public Employees Division Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 60)
  - Teamsters Law Enforcement League Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 61)
  - Teamsters Airline Division Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 62)
  - IBT Warehouse Division Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 63)
  - IBT Parcel & Small Package Division Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 64a-b)
  - IBT Motion Picture Division Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 65)
  - Teamsters Freight Division Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 66a-d)
  - Teamsters Local 20 Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 67)
  - IBT Local 20 Steward (Ohio State Silhouette) Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 68a-c)
  - Teamsters Local 20 Steward (Large, blue) Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 69)
  - Teamsters Joint Council 28/Local 38 Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 70)
  - Teamsters Local 63 Cream Colored Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 71)
  - Teamsters Local 63 Orange Colored Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 72a-b)
  - Teamsters Local 63 Cobalt Colored Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 73)
  - Teamsters Local 63 Freight Division Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 74a-b)
  - Teamsters Local 63 "Unity, Pride" American Flags Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 75a-d)
  - IBT Local 237, New York City and Long Island Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 76)
  - IBT Local 237 Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 77)
  - Teamsters Local 399, Hollywood CA Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 78a-b)
  - Local 435 "Teamsters Organizing for the Future" Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 79)
  - IBT Local 745 Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 80a-b)
  - Teamsters Local 745 Texas Longhorn Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 81)
  - Teamsters Local 853, San Leandro CA Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 82)
  - Teamsters Local 890, Salinas CA Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 83)
  - Jeweled Teamsters Logo Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 84)
  - Small Blue and White Enamel Teamsters Logo Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 85a-b)
  - IBT Logo Gold Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 86)
  - Copper Colored IBT Logo Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 87a-b)
  - Blue/Sky Blue/White Enamel IBT Logo w/ border Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 88a-d)
  - Printed IBT Logo Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 89)
  - IBT Retiree Pins, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 90a-b)
  - IBT 10 Years Membership Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 91)
  - IBT 20 Years Membership Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 92)
  - IBT 25 Years Membership Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 93)
  - IBT 50 Years Membership Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 94)
  - Local 295 Large IBT Logo Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 95)
  - IBT Logo Lapel Pin with Purple, Red, and White Ribbon, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 96)
  - Union Yes Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 97a-b)
  - Union Yes Ohio-Shaped Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 98)
  - Teamsters Pride - IBT Logo w/ American Flag - Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 99)
  - "We Support our Troops" IBT Logo/Flag Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 100)
  - "Buy American" Ford Logo/United Automobile Workers Logo Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 101)
  - IBT Logo "Women" Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 102a-d)
  - "A Woman's Place is in Her Union" Rosie the Riveter Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 103)
  - "Teamster Women" Yellow Rose Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 104)
  - JC 75 "Teamster Women" Palm Tree Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 105)
  - Vietnam Women's Memorial Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 106)
  - "Teamster Women on the Move for Good Jobs and a Better Future" Chicago Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 107)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 108)
  - "Ohio Women, the Heart of it All!" Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 109)
  - Teamsters D.R.I.V.E. Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 110a-c)
  - American/IBT Flag DRIVE Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 111a-b)
  - DRIVE Van-Shaped Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 112)
  - RISE Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 113)
  - Hard Hat Shaped "BM & CTD" IBT Logo Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 114)
  - IBT Logo/St. Jude Children's Research Hospital Burnished Metal Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 115)
  - IBT Logo/St. Jude Children't Research Center "Teamsters Support" Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 116)
  - St. Jude Children's Research Hospital Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 117)
  - St. Jude Children's Research Hospital Blue Enamel Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 118)
  - "W isn't for Working Families" Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 119)
  - Regina V. Polk Fund for Labor Leadership Lapel Pin, 1983; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 120)
  - "CLC/CTC" Canadian Labor Congress with Female Symbol Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 121)
  - American Red Cross "Labor/Red Cross on the Job Together" Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 122)
  - NSRA (National Street Rod Association) Safety 23 2000 Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 123)
  - NSRA (National Street Rod Association" Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 124)
  - ITWC (International Teamster Women's Caucus) Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 125a-b)
  - CLC/CTC (Canadian Labor Congress) Dec. 6 Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 126)
  - Australian Services Union (ASU) Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 127)
  - "Violence Against Women - There is No Excuse" AFSCME Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 128)
  - "Character Counts! Be Prepared for the 21st Century" Boy Scouts Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 129)
  - Boy Scouts Eagle/Fleur de Lis Logo Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 8, Item 130)
  - Bill Bradley for President Lapel Pin, 2000; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 1)
  - United Way Logo Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 2a-b)
  - Dollars Against Diabetes Snoopy Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 3)
  - Little Red Wagon Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 4)
  - Democratic Donkey Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 5)
  - "Attitude" Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 6)
  - USA Olypmic Rings Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 7)
  - Mall of America Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 8)
  - Corn Palace, Mitchell SD Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 9)
  - Edmonton Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 10)
  - Toledo Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 11)
  - New Orleans Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 12)
  - Planet Hollywood at Mall of America Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 13)
  - Iowa State Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 14)
  - Nebraska State Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 15)
  - Illinois State Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 16)
  - Indiana State Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 17)
  - South Dakota State Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 18)
  - Minnesota State Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 19)
  - Gary Fort Wayne, Indianapolis, Indiana Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 20)
  - Roadway Freight Truck Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 21)
  - IBT Logo Shield Lapel Pins/Medal Attachments, Undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Item 22a-d)